翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
So our SLList class now has these new fancy methods-- size and addLast,
我们的 SLList 类现在有了新的方法——size 和 addLast
but there are some issues.
但有一些问题
Both of them are pretty slow,
它们两个都很慢
and we're going to focus on the size method in this particular lecture
这节课我们重点讲解 size 方法
and discuss how to make it more efficient.
并讨论如何使其更有效率
So how slow is size?
size 有多慢呢？
Well, to maybe bring this to the forum and make you think about it in the following way.
也许可以将它带入论坛，让你从下述方式思考
Let's suppose size takes 2 seconds to process a list of size 1,000.
假设 size 处理大小为1000的列表需要2秒
That is, size-- which steps through the list one item at a time until it finally reaches the end--
也就是说 size 一项又一项的遍历到达尾部
is going to take 1,000 seconds.
需要1000秒
Now, you don't really know exactly how a computer works,
现在你并不是真的知道计算机是如何工作的
but just using your intuition, how long do you think it will take on a list of size a million?
但是仅凭直觉，你认为一个大小为一百万的 List 需要多久呢？
So ponder that for a moment.
仔细考虑这一点
So I say the answer is 2,000 seconds.
答案是2000秒
That if I have a list that's 1,000 times as large,
如果我有一个1000倍大的 List
then whatever the computer is doing inside--
那么无论计算机在里面做什么
and it has to step through the list--
它必须一步一步地遍历
it's going to have to do that 1,000 times as many times,
它将不得不这样做1000次
so it should take 1,000 times as many seconds for this total of 2,000.
所以应该是1000秒的1000倍——2000秒
So the more interesting question is how do we fix that?
更有趣的问题是我们如何解决？
And so I'm going to leave this as a puzzle for you that I'd really like you to ponder
我要把这作为一个谜题留给你们，我真的希望你们好好思考
to figure out a way to make size really fast no matter how big the list is.
想办法让 size 变得更快，不管 List 有多大
I don't care if there's a billion items. I want it quick.
我不在乎是否有十亿项，只想快点
So think about how you might do that,
想一想你会怎么做
and I will wait here patiently.
我会在这里耐心等待
So what I propose is that we-- instead of calculating the size on the fly every time size is called,
我的建议是，不要每次调用 size 都要遍历一次
which could take a long time,
这可能需要很长时间
we're going to set aside some information about the size up front.
我们打算预留一些关于 size 的信息
So I'm going to have private int size,
新建 private int size
and that's going to represent the current amount of information in the data structure.
这将表示数据结构中当前的信息量
So what's the size of a SLList of 1 item?
那么1个项目的 SLList 的大小是多少呢？
1.
What should I do whenever I add an item to the-- what should you change about the Size size plus equals 1.
每次新增一项时，size 应该加1
What about getFirst? Should the size change?
getFirst 呢？size 应该修改吗？
No.
不应该
AddLast.
AddLast
And indeed, we will add 1 to the size.
size 应该加1
I'll do it at the front.
放在前面
It doesn't matter where.
位置并不重要
So that is all we need for the size to be updated.
这就是我们更新 size 所需的全部内容
And so now we come to the size method.
现在我们来看看 size 方法
Well now, rather than calculate, I'm going to delete all this beautiful code we just spent so much effort discussing.
现在不需要计算了，我要删除花了这么多精力讨论的所有漂亮的代码
This code that speaks the secret language of the gods is going to be buried beneath the earth.
这个会说众神秘密语言的代码将被埋在地下
And instead, we're going to return size.
取而代之的是返回 size
That's pretty typical, right?
这很典型对吧？
Like, when you write a book of arcane evil from ancient gods,
就像写一本来自古代神灵的神秘邪恶之书时
or whatever, usually, once you're done with it,
通常情况下，一旦你做完了
you discard it to be discovered later at some day to destroy civilization.
丢弃它，等以后有一天被发现来摧毁文明
So we'll just say that's what we're doing.
这就是我们所做的
But we'll find that in later parts of this class,
但是我们会发现，在课程后面部分
and in the projects, you will actually be using that pattern of having the secret language of the gods.
在项目中， 你实际上将使用的是拥有神之语的模式
But here, it's actually easier for us
但在这里这样更容易
to just compute the size upfront and return it whenever we're ready for it.
提前计算大小并在需要的时候返回它
So now when we print out the size, we still get 4.
现在打印 size 仍然得到4
But it doesn't matter how big the list is.
List 有多大并不重要
This will be very fast.
这非常快
We did it.
我们做到了
So to debrief, basically, what we just did is we maintained a special size variable that caches the size of the list.
简而言之，我们刚才所做的就是维护了一个特殊的 size 变量来缓存 List 的大小
So any time the size of the list changes, we update it.
因此只要 List 的大小发生变化，我们就会对其更新
And caching is just a fancy term for putting aside some data to speed up retrieval at some later date.
缓存只是一个花哨的术语，意思是把数据放在一边，以便加快检索速度
It is redundant, but it also speeds us up.
它是多余的，但加快了速度
Now, it doesn't come for free.
它不是毫无成本的
There's this old saying that there ain't no such thing as a free lunch.
有句老话说，天下没有免费的午餐
We did have to do some work.
我们确实需要做一些工作
What we changed is that every time the size of the list is modified, we have to tweak the size a little bit.
每次修改 List 的大小时，都必须稍微调整一下 size
But it doesn't really have a meaningful impact on our performance, and for any practical circumstance that I can imagine,
但尽我所想，它对我们的表现并没有真正意义的影响
spreading that work of calculating the size over each add call,
将 size 的计算工作分散到每个 add 调用上
to me, is a net win in almost any case I can even imagine.
对我来说怎么都是净赚
Let's look at a visual that compares our naked recursive data structure with our SLList in the context of caching.
让我们在视觉上看一下缓存上下文在裸递归和 SLList 中的比较
So before, we said SLLists have this nice advantage
之前我们说 SLList 有个很好的优势
that whenever you want to manipulate the data
每当你想要操纵数据的时候
or see the data, you have to go through this middleman.
或者你想查看数据时，得通过这个中间人
This middleman provides you with very easy to understand methods that are guaranteed safe
这个中间人提供了非常容易理解并且保证安全的方法
and avoid you from shooting yourself in the foot in various ways.
避免你用各种方式砸自己的脚
Now, another nice advantage of the SLList structure to have this middleman
现在 SLList 结构拥有中间人的另一个优点是
is that it serves as a natural place
这是个很自然的空间
to store meta information about the entire list.
用来存储整个 List 的元信息
So for example, we can store the size of the list here.
例如我们可以在这里存储 List 的大小
It is technically redundant.
从技术上讲这是多余的
You can compute the size without this variable,
没有此变量也可以计算 size
but it speeds up the computation of size because you just need to return this value.
但它加快了 size 的计算速度，只需要返回此值
You can also store other things here, right?
你还可以在这里存放其他东西
Like you could store like the maximum, or the minimum,
比如最大值或最小值
or the largest value that was ever put in there,
或者是有史以来投入的最大价值
and those would also work.
而且这些也都有效
By contrast, with a naked recursive list, it's not so easy.
相比之下，使用裸递归 List 就不那么容易了
You could, in principle, do something like cache the size inside of each node.
原则上，你可以在每个节点内缓存 size
But even then, that means that any time you change something in the list,
但即便如此，只要你改变了 List 上的某些东西
you have to update a bunch of size variables.
就必须更新一系列 size 变量
You could also, for example, somehow, if you had a language that allows it,
你也可以...假如有这样一种语言
bind a variable up here that tracks the size of the whole thing.
允许在这里绑定变量跟踪 size
But in Java, there's no natural facility to do that.
但在 Java 中不行
So in effect, what you'll end up doing is having multiple variables that you have to keep straight.
其实你就是想维护多个变量保持不变
Here, this object-oriented programming approach means that we let the object control everything.
这种面向对象的编程方法意味着我们让对象控制一切
We tell the object,
我们告诉对象
your job is to not only do all of these tasks, but also to track the size for me.
你不仅要完成所有这些任务，还要帮我追踪 size
And in that way, it's just the natural way to organize our code.
这就是组织我们代码的自然方式
So again, the int list can do all the stuff than an SLList can do.
同样，IntList 可以做而 SLList 不能做的所有事情
But an SLList is going to be a more natural approach in nearly every way.
在 SLList 中几乎都有更自然的解决方式
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）